

Samih Y<u>oussef</u>

Web and mobile developer

CONTACT

+212 6 22 31 36 79

youssefsamih.tk

youssef.samih97@gmail.com

in youssef-samih

TRAINING

PUBLIC PROFESSIONAL LICENSE IN MEDICAL COMPUTING
University FS ain Chock
2018 – 2019

DIPLOME TS IN INFOMMATIC DEVELOPMENT

ISTA SPECIALIZED IN APPLIED TECHNOLOGY 2015 – 2017

DIPLOME BACCALAUREAT SVT

High school Omar Ibn Al Khatab 2014 – 2015

LANGUAGES

✓ Anglais : Well

✓ Arabe : Current

✓ French : Beginner

PROFILE

2 year and 2 months as a web and mobile developer at degitale agency and web marketing webeuz in the enumeration of recent technologies in development I am more passionate about all that corresponds to javascript development and these frameworks such as react, js node, express, and also wordpress, symfony.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

WEBEUZ | Web and Mobile Développer

Nov. 2017 - Juin. 2019

Tasks performed, back-end development of mobile applications (android and ios) with symfony framework and front-end with native reaction framework and redux: App e-Kaizen App Medix Training (in the Play Store); Web application development ohmylead.com (lead management); CRM Epiltech; General Company CRM Bank; website development with wordpress (see my portfolio for more details)...

WEBEUZ | Intern Web Developer

August. 2017 - Oct. 2017

Tasks performed, Plugin development and wordpress theme; Development of wordpress sites; application creation web in php and mysql (back-end); Participate as a team in the creation of website recrute.endev.ma

SKILLS

Php, C, C++, JavaScript

React, React native, Redux,
Bootstrap, Symfony, JQuery,
Node js (express)

HTML, CSS

SQL Server, MySQL,
Firebase, MongoDB

CERTIFICATION

MCPS sur HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery; 4 MCPS Sur SQL Server; SoloLearn En PHP; Openclassroom In SYMFONY, Information system & React native.